Gabriel Fernandez

Full-Stack Developer

Graduate of Coding Dojo Bootcamp, currently seeking new positions. Years of work experience, including two years for major tech companies. An agile learner that can pick up new technologies. Eager to integrate my work experience and my new set of skills.

EXPERIENCE

Apple (Contractor via Apex Systems)-GIS Researcher, Mar 2019 - Mar 2020

- Conducted web research and tracked upcoming construction projects and traffic/pedestrian-related changes + Analyzed aerial imagery + Contacted government and other sources for map updates.
- Improved workflow and streamlined work processes through regular feedback and consistent updates to project leaders and management.
- Maintained multiple projects of different priorities across multiple timelines to update Project Coordinators and our mapping team.

Oracle - Tax Operations Intern, Jan 2018 - Oct 2018

- Leveraged knowledge of Oracle's Business Intelligence tools to dissect the department's performance to guide leadership and improve strategic organizational growth process.
- Supported Oracle's tax planning, treasury planning, PMO, income tax compliance, withholding tax compliance, and non-income tax compliance teams with source to settle services.
- Processed service requests and coordinated with teams globally to control payments and ensure rendering of services were delivered and paid on time.

Mondelez International, Inc. - Associate, Jun 2017 - Jan 2018

 Ensured tactical and strategic success of store deliveries by facilitating the management of logistical work between drivers and client stores.

PROJECTS

Blogger — Repo | Website 2020

A blog post app where users can post blogs about certain subjects. Users have full CRUD functionality on their posts. Users can leave comments on posts. App also includes Admin functionality.

- Implemented user login/reg with Django Auth User and Django admin.
- Utilized Class-Based Views & reusable apps.
- Tech: Django, MySQL, Bootstrap, Crispy Forms, Pillow, FontAwesome, & Recaptcha.
- Deployed on AWS EC2, utilizing Nginx &Gunicorn.

My Shop — Repo | Website 2020

An eCommerce application where customers can search and purchase items. The admin can also manage customers' orders and products.

- Built application end-to-end using MERN stack.
- Implemented user login/registration.
- Implemented PayPal so customers can pay safely.
- Tech: React, Redux, MongoDB Atlas, Mongoose, Express, Node, BCrypt, JSONWebToken, Bootstrap, & PayPal.
- Deployed on Heroku

MovieDB API—Repo | Website 2020

Users can search for movies by utilizing the MovieDB API. The detail page displays key details about the movie.

- Retrieved data from MovieDB API.
- Tech: React, Redux, Axios, Framer Motion, Styled Components.
- Deployed on Firebase.

San Jose, CA

(408) 621-3339

gfernandez@ucdavis.edu

gabrielfernandezdeveloper.com

n gabriel-antonio-fernandez

ngabrfernandez

EDUCATION

University of California, Davis -Bachelor of Arts, 2017

• Economics & Political Science

Coding Dojo- Full Stack Web Development Certificate, 2020.

1000+ hours,
14-weeks Coding
Bootcamp | PYTHON,
MERN, JAVA.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Python, Java, SQL.

Frameworks/Libraries: Express, Django, ReactJS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Spring Boot.

Database: MySQL, MongoDB, SQLite.

Tools: Node.JS, Git, AWS EC2, Google Cloud Platform, Firebase, Heroku, BCrypt, Oracle's ERP, Postman, Sass(Syntactically Awesome Stylesheet).